{
    "id": "124d3ede251f41d0bd58c375b2595d62",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Give my love to Mira in case you ............................ her.",
            "description": "We normally use a simple present to refer to future in subordinate clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "will see"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The first time I ................................... him was last week.",
            "description": "The present perfect is not used with past time expressions. ",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house .................................... I was born in.",
            "description": "This is the house where I was born is also correct. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... a strange experience yesterday.",
            "description": "The simple present or present perfect cannot be used with past time expressions. ",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "have",
                "have had"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They ................................... married last month.",
            "description": "To simply say that something happened sometime ago, we use the simple past. ",
            "answers": [
                "got",
                "have got",
                "had got"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the man .................................. hit my dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who he",
                "he",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't think .................................... we will win.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "so that",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... the rain, they went out.",
            "description": "Either despite or in spite of is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Despite of",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... it was cold outside, she insisted on going.",
            "description": "Even if refers to future. However is not a conjunction. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got ..................................... hair.",
            "description": "Hair is uncountable in English. It cannot be used with a/an. ",
            "answers": [
                "a curly",
                "curly",
                "the curly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... she is late, we will leave without her.",
            "description": "In case is a conjunction it is followed by a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "In case",
                "In case of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You cooked ................................... more food than necessary.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "too much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}